<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
    <article>
        <title>The Value of Money</title>
        <img>img/money.jpg</img>
        <alt>Image of Plants in a Jar of Coins</alt>
        <desc>Do not become a slave to money.</desc>
        <text>We now live in a time where everything can be tied to money. Money is the goal of many people, but there is no coin in the world that has body heat.

Money it is cold, hard, round, and expressionless, but through it can reflect all the wonders of life. If the pursuit of wealth is only reflected in the accumulation of money figures, then our life will seem very mechanical and boring, and incomparably pale.

Do not become a slave to money. I believe that everyone agrees with this statement, and even struggles to master money, rather than being mastered by it. But you can't master it perfectly, when you have a certain desire to spend, your responsibility, commitment, wisdom, courage in front of money is unbearable, and can even collapse your whole life.

Improve your own ability now. Many people want to try something new but their own strength does not support, can only give up this thing. The improvement of your own ability also means that you can cultivate your own economic ability in this aspect of your own expertise, in simple terms is to realize their own ability. Only when you are strong, money will find you, rather than you trying to find money.

Money is not everything, but no money is everything. You just need to understand that you master money is not for money, but a responsibility to yourself is enough.

Money can't buy happiness, but happiness is dependent on money to maintain. The happy life we have now is built by our own hands, of which the sweet and sour only know themselves. There is no such thing as a quiet year, and if there is, it is definitely someone who is carrying the weight ahead of time. Don't let these people disappoint you, and don't disappoint yourself.
        </text>
    </article>

    <article>
        <title>GMO Food</title>
        <img>img/food.jpg</img>
        <alt>Image of Tomato being genetically modified</alt>
        <desc>GMO Foods both have two sides</desc>
        <text> The benefits of GMO foods include improved nutritional value, avoidance of pests, enhanced freshness, and affordable prices. The disadvantages of GM foods include allergic reactions, nutritional deficiencies, and increased drug resistance.

1. Benefits of GMO foods.
1. Increase in nutritional value: As one of the most scarce nutritional elements in the world, the increase in the content of iron helps the body to absorb iron. Previously, scientists have successfully introduced the ferritin gene from beans into rice through genetic modification technology to increase the iron content in rice and improve its nutritional value. There are also scientists cultivated genetically modified oilseed rape, containing a large number of high unsaturated fatty acids, with its refined vegetable oil can effectively improve blood microcirculation, nutrition and health.

2. To avoid pests: according to genetic modification technology with specific properties of genes such as insect resistance, weed resistance, resistance to adversity, etc. into the selected crops, so that they also have these characteristics of resistance to pests and diseases, indirectly reduce the use of pesticides and agriculture, and thus reduce environmental pollution, but also reduce the risk of pesticide residues on food, which is beneficial to human health.

3. Enhancement of freshness: GM technology can enhance the freshness of food, for example, by transferring the cold-resistant genes of fresh fish that survive in cold polar regions to perishable plants such as strawberries, so that they have characteristics that can survive in extremely cold environments and are also more conducive to freshness.

4. Affordable: GM technology on the one hand improves the yield of crops and on the other hand reduces the cost of producing crops, thus making GM food much cheaper than non-GM food in terms of price.

Bad effects of GMO food.
1. allergic reactions: genetically modified food has added foreign genes, resulting in new proteins, which may trigger an immune response in the body after eating the food, leading to food allergies, itchy skin, redness and swelling.

2. nutritional deficiencies: because of the uncertainty in the principle of gene action and the immaturity of gene technology, it may lead to gene mutations in the introduced species, causing changes in proteins and destruction of the nutritional structure, resulting in nutritional deficiencies.

3, increase drug resistance: when people consume genetically modified food transferred into antibiotic marker genes, the gastrointestinal microorganisms in the body will also produce antibodies to these antibiotic genes, thus making the efficacy of antibiotics used in the treatment process will be greatly reduced, and may produce antibodies to antibiotics, affecting human health and safety, etc.
( https://m.youlai.cn/jingbian/article/838B35mqEfJ.html )
        </text>
    </article>

    <article>
        <title>The View of World in 2100</title>
        <img>img/future.jpg</img>
        <alt>Image of Futuristic World</alt>
        <desc>What will the world look like in 2100?</desc>
        <text>According to the British newspaper "The Independent" reported on the 9th, the United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) released a report on the 9th, although the new crown epidemic makes this year's global greenhouse gas emissions reduced by 7%, but this reduction is not durable, such as the current trend can not be reversed, is expected to 2100, the global temperature will still rise about 3.2 ℃.   

The Paris Agreement sets the goal of holding the global average temperature rise to 2°C or less, and strives to keep it within 1.5°C. According to the British newspaper The Independent, some analyses suggest that a 3°C rise in global temperatures will lead to the extinction of a large number of organisms and make many areas of the world no longer suitable for human habitation, and 275 million people will face flooding due to rising sea levels. unep specifically reminds that the carbon dioxide emissions of the richest 1% of the world's population are equivalent to the emissions of the poorest 50% of the population combined, so the rich should take greater responsibility for combating climate change. In addition, governments around the world have the responsibility to actively promote a post-epidemic "green recovery" and strive to reduce greenhouse gas emissions by about a quarter by 2030, so that they can achieve the long-term goal of keeping temperature increases to 2°C or less.
Source: Global Times
        </text>
    </article>

</articles>